[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_03a_TalkTo_Grace_ReadyInterviews",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We have to start somewhere.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Now you're throwing my lines back at me? Never miss a chance to give me shite, do you?\\n\\nSo it is, though. We'll see what these folks have to say for themselves… let's just keep our expectations… low.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_04_TalkTo_Zander_FirstMeet",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That's Thorpe. I defeated him.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Hm. Even more impressive! But I cannot join the Crows right now - this sick little kitty has a greenish color and needs my help. \\n\\nWhat can I do? Little fellow's too weak to bring to a healer, and I cannot leave him here alone.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_04_TalkTo_Eynon_HelpSalve",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I need a cure for a poisoned lynx.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh no, another one with the green complexion? \\n\\nFirst a goat with potato eyes, then a bear with ears of corn! Animals turning into plants…  nature's a trickster, even for a druid, but I'd say someone's behind this.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Granny_Zander",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Won't or can't?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Clever, you. Too clever gets the cleaver, hm? Alright, you've got steel in your spine. \\n\\nDo me a favor, and I'll consider it. There's a church in Calvary, in Brightwood, it's under construction… for years now.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Marty",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How does that help the church?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yeah, well, I'm still sorting it all out, but it's coming clear, all right. \\n\\nClear as the wind coming through those great big holes in the roof!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Amis",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why would a specter need coin?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Don't you know about Brightwood? How they used to bury people alive? \\n\\nSo now there's one of them back for revenge, figures we owe him for all the suffering he's been through.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Dicun_Investigate",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Any idea why some of the money is missing?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "It could be anyone. The guards, Beatris, myself, none of us make much coin. Ah, but I'm not sure my opinion matters. \\n\\nI'm just happy they decided to restart the construction. It will be joyous to see this place restored.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Dicun_CaughtStealing",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I saw you taking the coin.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh no! No, no! Have mercy, please, don't tell Granny! \\n\\nI haven't touched a coin of what I took before, you'll see, I'll tell you where I hid it!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Granny_ZanderCanJoin",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Does it matter? You got your money.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ha! I get it! You're running your own little protection racket now, are you? \\n\\nI was going to hire you, but there's only enough room for one big fish in this pond. So get on with you - our deal is one and done.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CanJoin",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Uh, maybe later! Good enough you're here!\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Thank you. \\n\\nFor the second time in my life, I feel I have met a true friend.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest",
        "PlayerPrompt": "(Tell Zander about the priest)",
        "NPCResponse": "And you also made the priest make a confession? Ah ha ha! \\n\\nThat is what they call a \"metaphor,\" my friend.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!95_s01_05_DicunGetsAwayTimeline",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    }
]
